复杂语调：拿不准时，就重读名词。这是一段
Complex intonation, when in doubt, stress the noun. This is the beginning of an
美国英语的极其重要组成部分。
extremely important part of spoken American English. The rhythms and
这类长串名词和形容词的语调模式非常常见，
intonation patterns of the long streams of nouns and adjectives that are so commonly
这些练习会把形容词、名词和副词的语调模式结合起来，
used. These exercises will tie in the intonation patterns of adjectives, nice,
old, best, etc., Nouns, dog, house, surgeon, et cetera, and adverbs, very,
really、amazingly 等等。处理句子语调的一种方法，不是
really, amazingly, et cetera. One way of approaching sentence intonation is not to
从零开始构造每个句子，而是使用模式；每个模式都类似于
build each sentence from scratch. Instead, use patterns with each pattern similar to
数学公式。只不过不是代入数字，而是代入
a mathematical formula. Instead of plugging in numbers, however, plug in
单词。注意，音节重音和复合词重音之间有很大区别。
words. It's important to note that there's a major difference between syllable stress
在音节计数练习中，每个音节都用
and compound In the syllable count exercises, each syllable was represented
一个音符表示。在名词短语中，每个单独的词都会
by a single musical note. In the noun phrases, each individual word will be
由一个单一的音乐音符表示，不管总共有多少音节。
represented by a single musical note, no matter how many total syllables there may
有时，看起来像单音节的词会有更长的声音，
be. At times, what appears to be a single syllable word will have a longer sound to
例如，seed 要比 seat 读得更久。
it. Seed takes longer to say than seat, for example.